

CONTACT

- +92-342-0699570
- ☑ danishfayyaz21@gmail.com
- H#103-A, St# 24-B, Haji Qamerdeen qujarpura Lahore

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Project management
- Innovative
- Creative design
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Debugging

LANGUAGE

- English C2
- Urdu A1
- Arabic A2

HOBBIES

- Photography
- Design
- Writing
- Reading books

Muhammad Danish

SUMMARY

I'm a Software Engineer and have nearly 1 year of professional experience in making React websites. Looking forward to build my career in similar fields and always keen to work with teams of professionals who share same passion to achieve greater heights.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer at wellcreator | Dec 2021 till now **Main Projects**,

- City-book-web (A fully dynamic business listing web app build in react)
- City-book-app
- Autodeals
- AutoOnes

Internship at wellcreator | sep 2021 To Nov 2021

- Login system (with mailing system)
- Career portal
- Backup portal of databases

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science: | 2019-2023 | Continue

Government College University Lahore, GCUL

7th Semester

Intermediate (FSC Pre-Engineering): | 2017-2019 Government Degree College, Shalimar Lahore

Matric: | 2015-2017

Al madrassa higher secondary school, Lahore

Skills

Good in:

HTML, CSS ,JavaScript, C++

Knowledge of:

OOP, MySQL, MongoDB

Framworks: React js, Nodejs